<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iphone on Jason Madigan</title><link>/tags/iphone/</link><description>Recent content in Iphone on Jason Madigan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Even more iPhone first impressions (because I own this one)</title><link>/posts/2007-08-02-even-more-iphone-first-impressions-because-i-own-this-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2007-08-02-even-more-iphone-first-impressions-because-i-own-this-one/</guid><description>&lt;p>I had a nice surprise waiting for me when I arrived home yesterday. I was like a kid at Christmas opening the box for this thing. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been so excited about a gadget for a long time. As mentioned a few posts ago, I&amp;rsquo;d gotten to play with one at work over the past few weeks but nothing compares to owning one and getting to play with one on your own time. The design, as with all things Apple, is elegant, simple and gorgeous. The screen is amazingly bright and it&amp;rsquo;s resolution of 320x480 at 160PPI is incredible. In my spare time this evening I&amp;rsquo;ve toyed a little with some development/design for an iPhone interface for Runt. I&amp;rsquo;ll post some more about this over the next few days or whenever I get a chance. It means so much to have a real browser in a mobile phone.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>iPhone JTAG Interface discovered</title><link>/posts/2007-08-02-iphone-jtag-interface-discovered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2007-08-02-iphone-jtag-interface-discovered/</guid><description>&lt;p>George Hotz (geohot) over at #iphone.unlock on Undernet finally uncovered the iPhone Baseband&amp;rsquo;s (S-Gold 2) &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joint_Test_Action_Group">JTAG&lt;/a> interface, which means an unlocking solution (albeit hardware based for the moment) is within reach. Geohot initally thought the JTAG interface may have been been located in the dock, but his search proved fruitless. Accessing these traces is incredibly difficult because the board has many layers and blind via&amp;rsquo;s, and in the end could only be done by removing the S-Gold 2 from the baseband board altogether, which meant wrecking the board.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>iPhone - First Impressions</title><link>/posts/2007-07-11-iphone-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2007-07-11-iphone-first-impressions/</guid><description>&lt;p>At work today I finally got my hands on an iPhone. It was everything I&amp;rsquo;d
hoped for. Beautiful design, much smaller than I&amp;rsquo;d imagined and pretty
sturdy. I played around with viewing a movie, playing with the camera
and generally poking about the parts of the phone which didn&amp;rsquo;t require
the GSM radio. I want one. I mean, I wanted one before but without
having held and used one it&amp;rsquo;s very easy to dismiss purchasing it by
saying to yourself &amp;ldquo;Oh, I&amp;rsquo;ll wait, you know firsthand what first gen
Apple hardware is like&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;But, but 3G!&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m very tempted to take the
plunge and import one in the hope that the radio will get unlocked quite
soon.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Oh Steve</title><link>/posts/2007-06-13-oh-steve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2007-06-13-oh-steve/</guid><description>&lt;p>You cad, you.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>But but but you guys you don&amp;rsquo;t understand! A poorly written
application could crash AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;d sort of expected that Apple would end up giving developers access to
a Widget-like API for the iPhone. It&amp;rsquo;s disappointing that it turned out
to be true but I guess it&amp;rsquo;s sort of good news for dorky web developers
like me. It&amp;rsquo;s still a complete cop-out, though. Regardless of how neat
AJAX Web 2.0 (jesus I really hate referring to things as Web 2.0)
applications can be made to be to look and perform, it&amp;rsquo;s still
absolutely no substitute to having access to OS X&amp;rsquo;s core cocoa APIs such
as Core Image, Core Video, Core Audio and Core Animation (well, assuming
the iPhone is running Leopard). Which reminds me, I really should get to
leafing through that Objective-C book I bought a while ago.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>