<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scripting on Jason Madigan</title><link>/categories/scripting/</link><description>Recent content in Scripting on Jason Madigan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/scripting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding shopping list items via Home Assistant voice commands</title><link>/posts/2025-01-01-home-assistant-voice-shopping-lists/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2025-01-01-home-assistant-voice-shopping-lists/</guid><description>&lt;p>I recently got access to a couple of &lt;a href="https://www.home-assistant.io/voice-pe/">Home Assistant Voice Previews&lt;/a>, and wanted a way to quickly add items to my shopping list using voice commands. The built-in intents for adding todo list items are kind of wordy, and I liked how Alexa had a simple &amp;ldquo;Alexa add foo&amp;rdquo; shortcut to add items to a default shopping list.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After some tinkering, I came up with a simple setup that uses Home Assistant’s &lt;code>conversation&lt;/code> integration, &lt;code>intent_script&lt;/code>, and a few custom sentences to streamline the process.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Holiday time - bulk declining Google Calendar events</title><link>/posts/2017-07-03-declining-google-calendar-events-en-masse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-07-03-declining-google-calendar-events-en-masse/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m getting married in a few weeks, so recently I wanted a way to decline about 3 weeks worth of Google Calendar events en-masse. Since I was using Google Apps for our organisation&amp;rsquo;s calendar, I found the easiest way to accomplish this was to bust out some &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/script/start/">Google Apps Scripting&lt;/a>, which lets you script a number of Google Apps in your domain, including the &lt;a href="https://developers.google.com/apps-script/reference/calendar/calendar-event">Calendar&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>See an example below on how to bulk decline Google Calendar events using Google Apps Scripting - you&amp;rsquo;ll just need a calendar name &amp;amp; a date range and run this via the script console:&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>